wbwb.com.cn 2017-06-06

# HostEase Web Hosting

## Privacy Policy

Professional Hostease.com created this Privacy Policy to show our firm commitment to your privacy information.

### Information Collecting

We collect all the information about you (such as your name, address, IP address, E-mail, telephone number, credit card information and other billing information and the like ) that you give us in any way to provide you with corresponding service and notice you if there’s any significant change of our products and the service we provide. We may provide your personal information to the third party legally for necessary intention. You can refuse to disclose your private information, but once you provide it you consent to our legal use of the information. 

### Information Usage

We use the information you provide to complete our service, which may include new function notice, order completion, product shipment and so on. We will not share your personal information we collected with unrelated service providers without your permission. We may use non-identifying and aggregate information (such as the number of visitors we’ve got) for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of our website services, marketing, advertising and sales efforts, and to share with advertisers. We would not disclose any identifiable information. 

### With respect to the cookies

A cookie is a small string of text stored on your computer by a web browser. A cookie consists of one or more name-value pairs containing bits of information such as preferences, shopping cart contents, and the identifier for a server-based session, or other data used by websites.  
With the information we collect on your web site through the cookies, we can not only provide you with better service but also optimize our web site. 

### Our third party service provider

We, together with some other service providers, provide services to you. We will disclose the necessary personal information of you to the third party service provider to deliver programs, products, information and services. These parties are not allowed to use this identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

### Information Security

sWhile we cannot guarantee the loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur; we make every effort to protect your personal information from being stolen and misused. We encrypt you sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our web site with SSL(Security Socket Layer) technology.   
There may be links of other web sites on our web site and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of these web sites. 

### Your responsibility

You are responsible for the security of your ID and password. Do not share them with others. Always remember to log out after you finish working with your customer account to ensure that others cannot access your private information. Do not enter your customer ID and password on a public computer and take care even if on your private computer. 

### Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Once we make modification to this Policy, we will notice you by means of an E-mail or a notice on our home page. 

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please contact us at: info@hostease.com /live chat.
